<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home page on ena.rocks</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home page on ena.rocks</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 21:20:24 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>August Long Weekend</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/augustlongweekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 21:20:24 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/augustlongweekend/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;written over the days of 2025-08-01 to 2025-08-04&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-plan&#34;&gt;The Plan&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Leading up to the August long weekend, I was dreading it. I took friday off work in advance and monday was a civic holiday, so I was supposed to be looking forward to a 4 day weekend&amp;hellip; but I didn’t have any plans. My boyfriend Alex is going backpacking at Lake Superior and would barely have any signal, my local friends were all out of town, and it would be just me and my 2 cats (which I normally don&amp;rsquo;t mind). It’s also actually 3 cats, because I have to checkup on my friend’s cat occasionally to make sure she’s doing well and has water.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Users don&#39;t want AI, they want software that works</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/usersdontwantai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:51:34 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/usersdontwantai/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I wrote this almost 2 years ago, angry after a conference in a hotel room. I’ve cleaned it up a bit and added some recent events, but it remains largely unchanged.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When I was in university studying computer science all anyone wanted to talk about was ML. I was not that interested, but I noticed it more and more from students and recruiters and job listings. ML was going to change and improve everything about the world, drastically. I don’t think I heard anyone really propose a plan for that, the technology was still progressing. But of course, it was going to be the next big thing, all the companies and universities had to hop on it!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knitting and Crocheting my own Duke Sucellus slippers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/dukies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 13:05:09 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/dukies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I thought I’d start off easy with my first post, and share a pair of slippers I made based off an item in (old school) runescape. I took a lot of notes since I had to do everything twice to make a pair of slippers, so here is my pattern write-up.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I realize this is a really niche topic, this pattern requires you to:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;know how to knit&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;know how to crochet&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;like Old School Runescape&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;but I wanted to explore my thought process &amp;amp; how the project went, which I think can be universally applicable to a lot of different fibre craft backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/test-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 19:42:09 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/test-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello, I am a test!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Ena and I suppose I rock! I am a software engineer with a lot of hobbies, and this is my miscellaneous blog.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://mastodon.social/@enarocks&#34;&gt;mastodon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
